JENNIFER HOBBS

Linkedin: www.linkedin.com/in/jenhobbs204

I have a great deal of experience in the administration, travel and customer service industries having worked in both front and back of house roles. Extremely high attention to detail and excellent communication skills. Dedicated, motivated and not shy to push myself and others to achieve results. I have a passion for travel and am focused on maintaining a high level of service with clients and colleagues alike. In my spare time I am improving my knowledge of computer coding and am currently attending an online course in Web Development.

Career History:

DENMARK

Flight Centre LTD - March 2019 to Present

I currently work as part of the Flight Centre LTD Agile Project Team as a Subject Matter Expert (SME). Flight Centre has made the decision to move the global company onto a new booking engine platform. The Agile Project team 'Copernicus' has been created to ensure the companies requirements are communicated accurately, the new system is designed to match our needs and with minimal change for our agents on the front end. As an SME for content design I am expected to provide feedback on user stories, test the new system environments and communicate daily with teams based in Australia, USA, and UK.

BRITAIN

Flight Centre LTD – November 2017 to March 2019

Team Leader for Europe Content (GPN). I was expected to load and proof hotel and tour contracts into the calypso system for sale to Flight Centre agents globally. A great attention for detail is required as well as an understanding of the systems to ensure rates and inclusion details are loaded correctly. I was expected to maintain important relationships, with both internal selling businesses and external suppliers, analyse contracts and ensure the accuracy and development of my team. I also choose to be involved in the connectivity and systems testing aspect of this role. During my employment at Flight Centre I have completed the following in house training modules.

- Leadership Development Program (8 x 3 hours)
- Fierce Conversations (3 hours)
- Coaching for growth (3 hours)
- Managing Change (3 hours)

I have won multiple Customer Service and excellence awards as well as being invited to attend our Global Ball in Singapore 2016 and Berlin 2018. This is our most prestigious award available to only the top 10% of the company globally. During my time leading the team we won the outstanding achievement award and best North content team in January 2019. I also won the outstanding achievement award for project work in January 2020.

Flight Centre LTD – October 2015 to November 2017

Assistant Team Leader for Europe Content (GPN). As ATL I was expected to assist the Team Leader with implementing business plans and new processes. I was also expected to help develop team members alongside my normal daily responsibilities.

Flight Centre LTD – March 2014 to October 2015

Content Coordinator for the Global Procurement Network (GPN). As part of the Europe content team we were expected to load and proof hotel and service contracts into the calypso system. We were responsible for accurately delivering these products in a speedy manor to all selling partners across the world.

Flight Centre LTD - July 2013 to March 2014

International travel consultant trained to sell all holiday types to potential clients. This is done over e-mail, phone and by walk in. I was expected to tailor make holiday packages, sell these to potential clients, meet daily sales targets as well as use company systems and ensure all payments to suppliers were up to date.

AUSTRALIA

Nomads Hostel, Brisbane - January 2013 to May 2013.

Receptionist trained to use the company system checking in guests as well as independently and efficiently sorting out any issues customers had. I was expected to have an extensive knowledge of the area and give advice about places of interest and current events.

Rare Steakhouse, Melbourne - July 2012 to January 2013.

Head waitress expected to know the menu and wine list extensively and to anticipate customer needs. Also trained behind the bar, plating deserts, and making all hot drinks for customers. As head waitress I was also responsible for taking payments and cashing up at the end of the night.

NEW ZEALAND

Glasson's Ltd, Queenstown - September 2011 to May 2012.

As branch Supervisor I was expected to sell fashion products to targets and motivate my team to reach their targets. I was responsible for the opening and closing of the store including cashing up.

Addstaff Temping Agency, Queenstown - June 2011 to September 2011

Much of my work was waitressing/silver service at Banquets and Private functions for the Skyline Restaurant, Novotel, and the Events Centre. I also did basic office work such as temporary receptionist and front of house.

BRITAIN

Bumble Bees, Private Day Nursery, Kent - June 2010 to May 2011.

I was one of two key people responsible for a group of eight 2-year old's, using the Early Years Foundation Stages to structure the day, and solely responsible for planning the children's activities. We were also expected to give detailed feedback on each child's development whilst in our care.

Tigerlily Childcare Agency - April 2010 to June 2010

A childcare temping agency where I was sent out to any nursery institution in the area that needed last minute cover. I was often only informed of the workdays prior but could stay working in a nursery for anything from a day to a few weeks. I worked with all ages up to 5 years old. From this temping agency I was able to find a permanent position at Bumblebees in Kent.

CANADA

VANOC Retail Merchants, Whistler - February 2010 to March 2010.

Salesperson based at the Cross-Country Skiing Venue selling official merchandise for the Winter Olympics throughout the period of the games and the Paralympic Games.

The Westin Resort and Spa, Whistler (evenings) - June 2009 to April 2010.

Banquets waitress involving serving for different events and ensuring all customer food requirements were satisfied.

Ski Instructor, Blackcomb Mountain, Whistler – November 2008 to April 2009 December 2009 to April 2010.

A Whistler Kids Mini's Ski Instructor involved teaching 3 to 4-year old's with no ski experience to much higher skiing levels. I was also in charge of their safety and happiness in my care. I was expected to organise daily teaching strategies to encourage the children.

FRANCE

American School of Paris Summer Camp – June to August 2004. June to August 2005.

I worked at the ASP language summer camp in Paris. I worked with the 4 and 5-year-old bilingual children as a summer camp counsellor. I was expected to help improve their English language as well as encourage the children to participate and enjoy the daily activities.

Education and Qualifications:

2005 to 2008 - 2.1 BA (hons) Degree from University of Exeter, UK - Childhood and Youth Studies

2003 to 2005 - Hurtwood House School, Guildford, UK – A Levels – Art (A), Chemistry (B) & Biology (C) 1996 to 2003 – British School of Paris, France – GCSE Levels

2020 - HTML, CSS, and Web Design - General Assembly Circuits Course, Online

2019 - Introduction to Agile Project Management - Copenhagen, Denmark

2016 - Basic First Aid in the workplace - London, UK

2009 - Level One CSIA ski Instructors certificate - Vancouver, Canada

2008 - Basic Events Organising Course - University of Exeter, UK

Personal Skills and Interests:

IT Skills

Proficient in using Microsoft office applications (such as Excel), project management systems (such as JIRA, Salesforce, Ora) and hotel reservation systems (such as Calypso, Travelbox).

Interests

I am a keen snowboarder and try to go at least once a year. I enjoy socialising with my friends, baking and exploring new cultures across the world. In my spare time I am fascinated by Psychology and spend a lot of time listening to podcasts on society, culture, and crime.

Volunteer Work

From January 2017 to March 2018 I volunteered as a Samaritan in the Central London Office. During this time, I went through an intensive ten week active listening course and learnt to provide emotional support whilst broadening my experience of the world. I was on shift to answer phones once a week as well as being involved in their outreach programmes. These included supporting the Homeless and visiting the local Men's Prison to teach volunteer prisoners on how to become 'listeners' within the prison.